{"test_questions": [[{"question": "To make clean breast of", "opta": "To gain prominence", "optb": "To praise oneself", "optc": "To confess without of reserve", "optd": "To destroy before it blooms", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To keeps one's temper", "opta": "To become hungry", "optb": "To be in good mood", "optc": "To preserve ones energy", "optd": "To be aloof from", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To catch a tartar", "opta": "To trap wanted criminal with great difficulty", "optb": "To catch a dangerous person", "optc": "To meet with disaster", "optd": "To deal with a person who is more than one's match", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To drive home", "opta": "To find one's roots", "optb": "To return to place of rest", "optc": "Back to original position", "optd": "To emphasise", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To have an axe to grind", "opta": "A private end to serve", "optb": "To fail to arouse interest", "optc": "To have no result", "optd": "To work for both sides", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To cry wolf", "opta": "To listen eagerly", "optb": "To give false alarm", "optc": "To turn pale", "optd": "To keep off starvation", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To end in smoke", "opta": "To make completely understand", "optb": "To ruin oneself", "optc": "To excite great applause", "optd": "To overcome someone", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To be above board", "opta": "To have a good height", "optb": "To be honest in any business deal", "optc": "They have no debts", "optd": "To try to be beautiful", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To put one's hand to plough", "opta": "To take up agricultural farming", "optb": "To take a difficult task", "optc": "To get entangled into unnecessary things", "optd": "Take interest in technical work", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To pick holes", "opta": "To find some reason to quarrel", "optb": "To destroy something", "optc": "To criticise someone", "optd": "To cut some part of an item", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To leave someone in the lurch", "opta": "To come to compromise with someone", "optb": "Constant source of annoyance to someone", "optc": "To put someone at ease", "optd": "To desert someone in his difficulties", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To play second fiddle", "opta": "To be happy, cheerful and healthy", "optb": "To reduce importance of one's senior", "optc": "To support the role and view of another person", "optd": "To do back seat driving", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To beg the question", "opta": "To refer to", "optb": "To take for granted", "optc": "To raise objections", "optd": "To be discussed", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A black sheep", "opta": "An unlucky person", "optb": "A lucky person", "optc": "An ugly person", "optd": "A partner who takes no share of the profits", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "E", "explanation": "In the English language, 'Black sheep' is an idiom used to describe an odd or disreputable member of a group, especially within a family."}, {"question": "A man of straw", "opta": "A man of no substance", "optb": "A very active person", "optc": "A worthy fellow", "optd": "An unreasonable person", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To smell a rat", "opta": "To see signs of plague epidemic", "optb": "To get bad small of a bad dead rat", "optc": "To suspect foul dealings", "optd": "To be in a bad mood", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To hit the nail right on the head", "opta": "To do the right thing", "optb": "To destroy one's reputation", "optc": "To announce one's fixed views", "optd": "To teach someone a lesson", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "To do exactly the right thing; to do something in the most effective and efficient way."}, {"question": "To set one's face against", "opta": "To oppose with determination", "optb": "To judge by appearence", "optc": "To get out of difficulty", "optd": "To look at one steadily", "opte": "None of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}